deccanreport.com 2015-06-21

# Deccan report

Welcome to [Deccanreport.com](http://deccanreport.com/). The privacy of [Deccanreport.com](http://deccanreport.com/) users is important to us.  
**What information do we collect?**  
[Deccanreport.com](http://deccanreport.com/) does not collect or save any personal information.  
We do not place any cookies on the systems of visitors to our site.  
We will not disclose any personal information to any third party for any reason.  
We do not maintain any databases storing any personal information about our visitors.  
Since we do not maintain any personal information about our visitors, we will never send you any advertisements or unsolicited information about this site.  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.  
**Third party links & Downloads**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.We do link to other web sites which might support downloads of videos, images, software, games and any application files. We do not host any video content in our site,we display videos from video hosting sites.We are not responsible or liability for the copyright issues of videos content.  
**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website in Terms & conditions.  
**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification..
